{"exam":[{
    "question": "Wedge compression fracture of first thor vertebra, sequela",
    "option1": "Cormorant, pied",
    "option2": "Phalacrocorax varius",
    "option3": "Realfire",
    "option4": "bandcamp.com",
    "answer": 4,
    "description": "Computerized Tomography (CT Scan) of Left Toe(s)",
    "id": "a5278420-9379-4845-8df7-1f15e1d80a64"
  }, {
    "question": "Sltr-haris Type I physl fx upr end humer, r arm, 7thG",
    "option1": "Musk ox",
    "option2": "Ovibos moschatus",
    "option3": "Meetz",
    "option4": "utexas.edu",
    "answer": 1,
    "description": "Excision of Left Upper Arm Muscle, Percutaneous Approach",
    "id": "fe833bb7-3068-4cc3-81c0-a5d267a3fd55"
  }, {
    "question": "Nondisp subtrochnt fx unsp femr, init for opn fx type 3A/B/C",
    "option1": "Yellow-bellied marmot",
    "option2": "Marmota flaviventris",
    "option3": "Npath",
    "option4": "vistaprint.com",
    "answer": 3,
    "description": "Beam Radiation of Sinuses using Neutrons",
    "id": "e1aeba4b-ee51-4e3a-b6d0-08c9c3bfc0df"
  }, {
    "question": "External constriction of right elbow, sequela",
    "option1": "Black-capped chickadee",
    "option2": "Parus atricapillus",
    "option3": "Realblab",
    "option4": "ifeng.com",
    "answer": 4,
    "description": "Removal of Intraluminal Device from Upper Intestinal Tract, Via Natural or Artificial Opening Endoscopic",
    "id": "85eaf82f-8592-41eb-adbd-402084cb7271"
  }, {
    "question": "Corrosion of third degree of unspecified ear",
    "option1": "Tern, arctic",
    "option2": "Sterna paradisaea",
    "option3": "Thoughtbridge",
    "option4": "wikia.com",
    "answer": 1,
    "description": "Revision of Autologous Tissue Substitute in Left Carpal, Percutaneous Endoscopic Approach",
    "id": "89411288-a236-4f93-a466-a0a4718aa9b5"
  }, {
    "question": "Anterior cord syndrome at T2-T6, subs",
    "option1": "Lemur, ring-tailed",
    "option2": "Lemur catta",
    "option3": "Zoovu",
    "option4": "odnoklassniki.ru",
    "answer": 4,
    "description": "Revision of Drainage Device in Scrotum and Tunica Vaginalis, Open Approach",
    "id": "3a9e77e6-1ebd-4606-9055-370166883f1e"
  }, {
    "question": "Dislocation of MCP joint of right thumb, sequela",
    "option1": "Roseat flamingo",
    "option2": "Phoenicopterus ruber",
    "option3": "Rhyzio",
    "option4": "sitemeter.com",
    "answer": 2,
    "description": "Insertion of Spacer into Right Temporomandibular Joint, Percutaneous Endoscopic Approach",
    "id": "b6609b0e-c80f-476b-84a1-41cda8a00397"
  }, {
    "question": "Inj long flexor musc/fasc/tend thumb at wrist and hand level",
    "option1": "Openbill stork",
    "option2": "Anastomus oscitans",
    "option3": "Katz",
    "option4": "com.com",
    "answer": 2,
    "description": "Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI) of Right Breast using Other Contrast",
    "id": "8ac62d67-e119-4b6b-af77-4daca87b404e"
  }, {
    "question": "Contact with hot water in bath or tub, initial encounter",
    "option1": "Native cat",
    "option2": "Dasyurus viverrinus",
    "option3": "Topicshots",
    "option4": "vimeo.com",
    "answer": 4,
    "description": "Fluoroscopy of Right Knee using Low Osmolar Contrast",
    "id": "f07c71ac-4731-4756-ad65-33fd0fe1e3eb"
  }, {
    "question": "Contact with hot food, sequela",
    "option1": "Spoonbill, european",
    "option2": "Platalea leucordia",
    "option3": "Demizz",
    "option4": "joomla.org",
    "answer": 1,
    "description": "Destruction of Sacral Sympathetic Nerve, Percutaneous Endoscopic Approach",
    "id": "367854c9-3936-4285-a02d-acc86b9b00ef"
  }, {
    "question": "Anaplastic large cell lymphoma, ALK-neg, intrathorac nodes",
    "option1": "American Virginia opossum",
    "option2": "Didelphis virginiana",
    "option3": "Edgepulse",
    "option4": "ihg.com",
    "answer": 2,
    "description": "Compression of Face using Intermittent Pressure Device",
    "id": "d8b2a658-cbfc-4a72-aa67-7d7f22078263"
  }, {
    "question": "Oth fx shaft of rad, left arm, subs for clos fx w malunion",
    "option1": "Currasow (unidentified)",
    "option2": "Crax sp.",
    "option3": "Browsetype",
    "option4": "netlog.com",
    "answer": 3,
    "description": "Insertion of Spacer into Thoracic Vertebral Joint, Percutaneous Endoscopic Approach",
    "id": "e3a68ab7-f6f0-4568-abd7-b6a5ef64852e"
  }, {
    "question": "Complete physeal arrest, right proximal tibia",
    "option1": "Sociable weaver",
    "option2": "Philetairus socius",
    "option3": "Abata",
    "option4": "live.com",
    "answer": 1,
    "description": "Removal of Implantable Heart Assist System from Heart, Open Approach",
    "id": "fd2e0d07-e409-4510-8338-dc6381a24756"
  }, {
    "question": "Charcot's joint, unspecified hand",
    "option1": "Ibex",
    "option2": "Capra ibex",
    "option3": "Wikibox",
    "option4": "fda.gov",
    "answer": 1,
    "description": "Reposition Right Radial Artery, Percutaneous Approach",
    "id": "65c96ba0-00c5-4e2f-ba6a-170a372f8dac"
  }, {
    "question": "Periodontal disease, unspecified",
    "option1": "Squirrel, pine",
    "option2": "Tamiasciurus hudsonicus",
    "option3": "Camido",
    "option4": "comcast.net",
    "answer": 3,
    "description": "Tomographic (Tomo) Nuclear Medicine Imaging of Abdomen and Pelvis using Fluorine 18 (F-18)",
    "id": "ba5d6395-0426-4131-a1ab-b540da3d8383"
  }, {
    "question": "Nondisp seg fx shaft of r fibula, 7thG",
    "option1": "Black-fronted bulbul",
    "option2": "Pycnonotus nigricans",
    "option3": "Jabberbean",
    "option4": "stumbleupon.com",
    "answer": 3,
    "description": "Fluoroscopy of Bilateral Upper Extremity Veins using Low Osmolar Contrast",
    "id": "c45da4fa-2339-423c-91df-91c5920e5f37"
  }, {
    "question": "Sequelae of protein-calorie malnutrition",
    "option1": "Lourie, grey",
    "option2": "Lorythaixoides concolor",
    "option3": "Zoombox",
    "option4": "fda.gov",
    "answer": 3,
    "description": "Removal of Intraluminal Device from Kidney, External Approach",
    "id": "ab10c276-ff46-41e0-9e9a-4ccde6344f05"
  }, {
    "question": "Disp fx of dist phalanx of l mid fngr, 7thG",
    "option1": "Fowl, helmeted guinea",
    "option2": "Numida meleagris",
    "option3": "Agivu",
    "option4": "mayoclinic.com",
    "answer": 3,
    "description": "Bypass Left Lacrimal Duct to Nasal Cavity, Percutaneous Approach",
    "id": "c0454fd0-069d-404c-a199-923cc9781a3c"
  }, {
    "question": "Oth fx unsp low leg, 7thJ",
    "option1": "Capybara",
    "option2": "Hydrochoerus hydrochaeris",
    "option3": "Yodel",
    "option4": "artisteer.com",
    "answer": 3,
    "description": "Destruction of Bilateral Fallopian Tubes, Open Approach",
    "id": "087af045-b8c1-4946-8234-b35bee6e9473"
  }, {
    "question": "Displaced transverse fracture of left patella",
    "option1": "Lion, asian",
    "option2": "Panthera leo persica",
    "option3": "Thoughtworks",
    "option4": "1und1.de",
    "answer": 1,
    "description": "Removal of Drainage Device from Left Shoulder Joint, External Approach",
    "id": "8d829141-8375-485d-8ad7-4aa15da40cd7"
  }]
}
